<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Moovit</string>
    <string name="terms_1">• Routes and Services: The app may not include information about all bus routes and services available. Moovit reserves the right to add or remove bus routes and services from the app without prior notice. Moovit will make commercially reasonable efforts to keep the app up to date with accurate information about bus routes and services. You acknowledge and agree that the availability of bus routes and services may vary from time to time and that Moovit is not responsible for any discrepancies or errors in the information provided on the app.</string>
    <string name="terms_2">• User Information: To use the app, you will be required to provide personal information including your national identification card number, payment details such as CVV number and card number, and details of the route and dates of your journey. You agree to provide accurate and complete information and to update your information as necessary.</string>
    <string name="terms_3">• Data Protection: Moovit is committed to protecting your personal information and respecting your privacy. Moovit will collect, use, and store your personal information in accordance with applicable data protection laws and regulations. Moovit will not share your personal information with third parties except as required by law or with your explicit consent.</string>
    <string name="terms_4">• Use of the App: The app may be used solely for the purpose of booking bus passes. You may not use the app for any other purpose or in any way that violates applicable laws or regulations.</string>
    <string name="terms_5">• Availability of the App: Moovit will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the app is available at all times. However, Moovit does not guarantee that the app will be available without interruption or that it will be error-free.</string>
    <string name="terms_6">• Payment: Payment for bus passes will be made through the app using the payment details provided by you. Moovit will use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of your payment information. However, Moovit does not guarantee the security of your payment information and is not liable for any unauthorized use of your payment information.</string>
</resources>